[Taiki] Chinatsu has been staying with us
for just over a month now.
[alarm beeping]
Mm?
[alarm continues beeping]
[pleasant music playing]
Good morning.
[Taiki] My eyes have almost acclimated
to her blinding radiance.
I washed your sports gear,
so take it upstairs with you.
[Taiki] I used to hit
the snooze button five times,
but it's down to just twice these days.
Oh, man. Having a crush on someone...
feels great!
[opening theme song playing]
BLUE BOX
EPISODE 4
IF HE WINS
Thank you for the meal.
- [Kyo] The match is tomorrow, right?
- Yup!
Then why are you so peppy?
You know, I think I'm just
living each day to the fullest.
Seems like things have
settled down pretty quick.
What?
No, what I mean is...
with a man and a woman
living under the same roof,
I'm surprised nothing has happened yet.
Well, the thing is...
- [phone chimes]
- Huh?
CHINATSU KANO
SORRY TO BOTHER YOU!
- Chinatsu!
- [phone chimes]
DID YOU TAKE MY UNIFORM BY ACCIDENT?
[amusing music playing]
KANO
[gasps, whimpers]
I HAVE GYM FIFTH PERIOD...
I'll take it to her now!
I'LL BRING IT TO YOU!
WHERE SHOULD WE MEET?
SOMEWHERE SECLUDED WOULD BE BEST, RIGHT?
HOW ABOUT THE AV ROOM?
ROGER THAT
[Taiki] Shoot. It's 'cause
I was rushing this morning.
I can't let anyone see us.
It'll need to be quick.
- [Haryu] If it isn't Taiki.
- [gasps]
[grunts]
Why are you avoiding me?
It's not what it looks like, I promise.
Perfect timing.
Let's get some practice in.
Uh, I'm really sorry.
I'll work extra hard at practice later!
He got away from me.
AV ROOM
[footsteps running]
[Taiki] There's usually no one in here.
Taiki?
[exclaims] Hina!
What are you doing in here?
Why do you ask?
RHYTHMIC GYMNASTICS MEETING
Rhythmic gymnastics has a meeting.
[Taiki] Come again?
[Hina] So what do you want?
Oh, no, it's nothing.
[gasps]
- Oh, you dropped--
- Don't touch that!
Listen to me!
You cannot touch that!
Why not?
Hmm... Ahhh...
- Ahhh... [giggles]
- [Taiki groans]
Well, if you must know,
that's actually my dirty tracksuit
from junior high.
[gasps]
- [Hina] Remove yourself.
- [Taiki] Right.
[Hina] Hm? Wait a minute, Taiki.
This is what you wore
for gym class, wasn't it?
I mean, when we were in junior high.
You're right.
I haven't washed it once since then.
[Hina] Be gone.
[Taiki] Understood.
[footsteps]
[Taiki] Oh, man.
Why are there people everywhere I go?
INOMATA
At this rate, she's gonna
have to wear my tracksuit!
I'm running out of time.
CHINATSU KANO
NEW MESSAGE
What?
Come to the roof on the west side?
NO TRESPASSING
[wind blows]
Oh, there you are.
Thank goodness.
Glad we could work this out.
How do you have the key to this door?
Oh, my friend is in the Astronomy Club.
Here.
You're a lifesaver. Thanks so much.
[Taiki] So, this is Chinatsu at school.
[Chinatsu] Hm?
Nothing.
[school bell chiming]
Oh, no! Chinatsu,
if we don't hurry, we'll miss class!
What are you doing?
I thought I would just change here,
since there isn't any time.
Right here?
Oh, it's okay.
Sports club girls get accustomed
to being comfortable
changing just about anywhere we can.
That is not what I meant.
I'll keep an eye out for anyone coming.
Thank you.
[Taiki] It's not anything new,
but she's so careless.
Does she not have any idea
everyone thinks she's adorable?
[clothes rustling]
Huh?
Oh, geez.
Hearing what's going on...
my imagination's running wild.
For real?
- Yeah, and then...
- What?
[Chinatsu grunts]
[piano music playing]
[Taiki grunting]
Thanks for waiting!
Are you okay?
If you'd been ten seconds later,
I would have been screwed.
Let's head out.
That's fine, you go ahead.
Okay, sure thing.
Thank you, Taiki.
[Taiki] If she's okay
with undressing in front of me...
I guess she doesn't really
see me as a guy.
[sighs]
I need to step up my guy game.
[boy 1] See ya tomorrow.
[boy 2] Anyone have the birdies?
[boy 3] What time
are we meeting tomorrow?
- [Hina] Taiki!
- Hm?
Regional prelims start tomorrow, huh?
Don't go so hard
that you mess up and look like an idiot!
Stay in your own lane!
[Hina giggles]
I'm gonna get Kyo to film it.
You know, I always thought
that you and her...
No way.
Is that so?
Anyway, you don't need
to get all worked up.
Playing doubles with me,
there's no way we'll lose.
[Taiki] He's so confident.
And next week in singles,
all you need to get is in the top 16.
Yeah, it's no problem.
I'm a lot stronger than I was before.
I can get top eight, maybe four.
Yeah, that's cool.
You know you left your racket bag.
[Taiki exclaims]
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I was waiting for you to notice.
I'll be right back!
[Yukiko] Taiki, make sure
you pack your uniform.
And definitely don't forget
your racket and your shoes.
I've got 'em.
- And... Mmm... Oh...
- Watching my mom at moments like these...
there's no doubt I'm her son.
You need towels! How about eight?
I don't need any.
I already packed up everything myself.
Are you sure?
[gasps]
Taiki!
[whimpers]
- [Yukiko] To the laundry!
- Gimme that towel!
[Yukiko] Here, catch!
Ahh! Come on, quickly, quickly!
[Taiki] Am I okay?
It is my first high school match,
but I've been in tournaments before.
Why am I so nervous?
I gotta chill out.
If I lose 'cause of some dumb mistakes,
it's not gonna be funny.
I have no reason
to feel this much pressure...
[muffled screaming]
[grunts]
When you get worried, get exercising.
You're going to nationals, right?
Get it together, Taiki.
[grunts]
[Chinatsu] Well, you're practicing late.
[Taiki] Chinatsu.
I felt restless, so I'm...
practicing.
Uh, Taiki...
your shirt is on inside out.
[exclaims]
[Taiki] Maybe I'm just not
cut out for this.
[gasps]
[Chinatsu sighs]
[grunts]
Oh, I'm sorry!
Chinatsu has no issue
changing in front of me...
but she cares about this?
Taiki, you've got...
I what?
It's just, you have a six-pack.
[Taiki] She noticed that?
I mean, you do work out all the time.
Come to think of it,
even Haryu was mentioning to me
that you've been bulking up lately.
Well, having more muscle doesn't exactly
make you that much better at badminton.
Huh?
You're pessimistic.
What? [groans]
- Earth to Taiki.
- Hm?
What is it?
Hyakue.
- [screams] What?
- Oh.
They say Hyakue is an acupressure point
on your head that can help you to relax.
There's no benefit
to panicking the day before,
and you've been working so hard
the past few weeks.
Don't drive yourself crazy overthinking.
You just gotta show 'em
what you're made of.
Is that clear?
Crystal.
This pressure point... really does work.
[Chinatsu] And...
don't worry you're still
going to have next year,
and the year after that, too, Taiki.
[Taiki] But Chinatsu will have graduated
the year after next.
You're going to keep
getting even stronger!
- That's not good enough for me.
- Huh?
[exclaims softly]
Good night, Chinatsu.
All right!
Let's do this!
Seems like you got over your nerves.
I don't have time to be nervous.
Hmph!
[chuckles] I like it.
[announcer on PA]
Attention all participants:
The doubles matches will begin shortly.
ROUND 1
[referee] Out!
ROUND 3
ADVANCED TO BEST 16
- Weird.
- What?
It just feels like it's too easy.
We aren't losing the regional prelims,
'cause you're paired with me.
Could we have
the winner's signature, please?
I guess this certainly shows
a lot of your weak points
we'll need to work on later.
[uplifting music playing]
[Taiki] He's right. To be honest,
there were plenty of moments
during the match
where I felt like Haryu saved me.
- [boy] Yeah!
- [grunts]
[grunts]
- [Taiki] So loud!
- Yeah!
- And bold moves, too!
- [yells]
Then, he's unexpectedly calm.
Well, that's taken care of!
Huh?
- Let's go.
- Yep.
That you, Harry?
You are Kengo Haryu, right?
The one who used to be
in the KTS Junior group?
[Haryu] You got the wrong guy.
You're a liar and a cheat!
Hyah!
You know each other?
Yeah, this guy was
my doubles partner in junior high.
Shoichiro Kishi
from Shimotomi High School.
Well, he just called you
a liar and a cheat.
Yeah, and I can't think of why.
[Kishi] It's because Harry here
broke his promise.
This conman said that he'd give me
Chinatsu Kano's phone number
and then totally didn't!
Huh?
The deal was,
I'd do it only if you beat me.
I did beat you.
Not in an official match.
So then, you're just
an acquaintance of Chinatsu?
Huh? Eh, sorta.
I'll never forget it.
It was last year,
when I went to Eimei's school festival.
SCHOOL FESTIVAL
[Kishi] My wallet's gone!
No! It was limited edition!
- [Chinatsu] Excuse me!
- Hm?
[gasps softly]
[anime pop song playing]
My anime idol had come to life
out of my wallet!
Which anime?
Don't engage with him.
After that, someone told me
that she was a friend of Harry's,
so I asked him to introduce us.
But your buddy here
never followed through.
Terrible, right?
Isn't he the absolute worst?
[Taiki] You made the right call, Haryu.
[inhales sharply] So today,
I'm gonna crush you
in the doubles matchup,
and then you'll finally
introduce us for real!
- [boy] Kishi.
- Hm?
I have...
a really nasty stomachache...
[groans]
I can't... go on...
[siren wails]
Yokoyama!
Good thing you made it
through the qualifiers.
Okay, that's fine!
We'll settle it in singles next week!
I'm not playing in the regional prelims.
So, our next official match would be...
Prefectural qualifiers in June.
June? No, I'll find a sub right now,
and we'll settle this.
- Not gonna happen.
- You can't leave till we play.
Okay, okay, I get it.
If you can beat Taiki
in next week's singles match,
I'll give you her phone number.
[Taiki groans]
Well, actually, I'm gonna ask her
if I can give it to you.
- You just get to decide?
- Uh, Taiki?
Yeah. My partner, the guy behind you.
Hm.
Hmm.
[tense music playing]
I've already won!
Huh?
I wonder what I should I text her first!
♪ La-la-la-la-la! ♪
- [Taiki grunts]
- Better watch out.
He may act like that,
but he's quite the strong player.
[grunts angrily]
You're the worst!
[birds chirping]
[Taiki] Why do I have to do this?
It's not like I want Kishi
to have Chinatsu's number either, but...
I didn't want to get dragged
into that mess.
- [Chinatsu] That's right.
- [Yukiko] Mmm-hmm.
- That's why Taiki...
- That's Chinatsu.
...the other day...
[Taiki] I'd feel awkward
seeing her right now.
And yesterday,
I probably came off a bit harsh.
I'm just wrapped up in wanting
to get to nationals this year.
[Yukiko] I'm glad to hear that Taiki won.
[Chinatsu] He worked really hard for it.
Even at home, he works on swings
instead of his homework.
He's just got to win.
Besides, I already made
pork cutlets for dinner tonight.
He shouldn't "pig out" if he lost.
To be honest, I've been a little worried...
that he's working himself too hard.
He's got a whole two years left,
but it seems like
he's been in such a hurry.
[Chinatsu] Exactly.
I said the same thing to him.
That he still has two years left.
Ever since I said that, though,
he has seemed a bit off.
He's always like that.
[Taiki] Leave me alone.
[Chinatsu] Oh, no. I get why he's angry.
I realized afterwards,
he might have thought
that I was telling him
it's okay to lose this year.
[Taiki] Well, actually...
I was just feeling a bit low,
because it made me see
the age difference between us.
[Yukiko] Well, surely, that wasn't
your intention in saying it, right?
Of course not!
Well, then, you have
nothing to worry about.
[Chinatsu] I suppose, but...
for me,
last year really flew by
in the blink of an eye.
I feel like it came and went
before I even knew it.
When I think how
I only have one more year left,
I can't help but feel
a bit envious of Taiki.
What I said wasn't exactly encouraging,
it was really me voicing
my own fears and anxieties,
and I feel bad now.
Chinatsu, you're one of the good ones.
[gasps]
No, I'm really not, though.
Such a kind soul.
[door opens]
[Taiki] I'm home.
Oh! Welcome back!
Congratulations!
Thanks, Mom.
You must've had a good partner.
That wasn't all it was.
Just watch...
I'm gonna win singles, too!
[Yukiko] No need to shout about it.
[Taiki breathes heavily]
I'm gonna put my stuff down.
He's always on to the next thing.
[Taiki] If Chinatsu is feeling uneasy,
then it's all the more reason
for me not to lose.
I seriously wonder
where he gets all that confidence from.
Oh, and don't worry about him,
he's just being Taiki.
No, I...
I believe there's actually
a lot we can learn from each other.
[Taiki] Here's to a good match.
- [Taiki and Kishi] Rock, paper...
- Things are heating up already.
They're just deciding
who's gonna serve first, dude.
So, Haryu, I hear you initiated
some weird contest.
Don't worry,
I won't give him her number
unless she wants me to.
I think she'd be too considerate
to say anything.
And anyway,
I expect Taiki to win this.
Wait, you do?
Obviously. I've been raking him
over the coals in training.
[in a scary voice] And if he loses,
he's got another thing coming.
I sense something!
GIVE YOUR ALL
[Kyo] Boy, am I glad
I'm not Haryu's partner.
[referee] First game! Love all. Play!
[grunts]
[thrilling music playing]
Taiki's improved,
but his opponent
sure looks pretty strong, huh?
He can really put some weight
behind his smashes.
You can't just keep returning them.
[both grunting]
All right!
[grunts]
- [girl] Oh, we found you!
- Huh?
[Haryu] The girls' basketball team.
What are you doing here?
We had a practice match
close by at Kita High,
and heard there was
a badminton tournament.
- Are any of ours up?
- [Haryu] My partner, a first year.
[girl] Oh, Taiki.
Well, team, let's cheer him on!
[grunts]
So, is it because we showed up?
He's been on defense the whole time.
Yeah, there are definitely
people who are like,
"Figure skaters always mess up
when I'm watching", you know?
I think we're seeing his strategy.
[girl] Strategy?
[Haryu] It can take a while
to get used to the speed of smashes.
Taiki starts off slow,
so in the beginning,
he focuses on defense,
and waits for his opponent to tire out.
If you look, he's moving his opponent
around the court with each return.
This guy is finally starting to use
his head when he's on the court.
- [announcer] Match 15 is about to begin.
- I better get going.
Sure thing. Good luck!
- [Kyo] You're not gonna get closer?
- Oh.
Here's fine.
I know a little about your situation.
Taiki told me you two talked.
He said that he told you
because he trusts you.
[gasps]
[Kyo] She is undoubtedly adorable.
It seems like competitions
are always tense.
Like there's a different weight
behind every single shot.
[Kyo] Mm.
Yeah. Hey, by the way,
did you know that your phone number
is apparently at stake for this match?
Huh?
I'll tell you that your classmate Haryu
is the one who started the whole thing.
He's the one to complain to.
CHII
But there's nothing in it
for Taiki if he wins.
So, Chinatsu...
if he wins this match, could you
take him somewhere, like the aquarium?
What?
We won't be able to use the gym tomorrow,
and the clubs will be cancelled.
Not to mention,
part of the reason he's doing so well
is because of your influence.
[Chinatsu] I don't think
I influence people.
You certainly do.
The determination to stay behind in Japan
and compete in nationals!
Someone was in the gym early this morning.
I'm gonna go, too!
He's an easily influenced lad.
He's the type that, once he sets
his mind on something, he goes all out.
And I can say as his friend,
that lately, I've seen him
working harder than ever.
I don't think the old Taiki would've been
able to land that kind of shot.
I believe it's because
he has someone in his life
who has the same goal.
It helps him push himself,
to keep working harder.
So when he gets
a step closer toward that goal,
I think it would help him
to get something in return.
[motivational music playing]
[grunts]
[gasps]
Yeah, let's go!
[Kyo] He's fired up!
[Chinatsu] Okay.
If he wins, I'll ask him...
to the aquarium.
[closing theme song playing]